30 years after the murders, the brothers tell their story.
The Menendez Brothers is a documentary film directed by Alejandro Hartmann.
Serving life in prison for murdering their parents, Lyle and Erik Menendez speak out
in this documentary explaining the shocking crime and ensuing trials.
Self (voice), played by Erik Menendez.
Self (voice), played by Lyle Menendez.
Self, played by Robert Rand.
Self, played by Shelley Ross.
Self, played by Pamela Bozanich.
Self, played by Alan Abrahamson.
The Menendez Brothers is a 2024 American true crime documentary film directed by Alejandro Hartmann for the streaming company Netflix, in
which brothers Lyle and Erik Menendez, who were convicted of the 1989 murders of their parents, are interviewed about the case.
The film explores themes of based on true story,
murder, true crime, crime, compassionate.